(Lucy(by text):)Sorry, auto-correct.
That was supposed to say "I like sports."
(Leonard:)I never wanted to play the cello.
(Leonard:)How do you meet girls playing the cello?
"Hey, wanna come over to my house
and hear me play an instrument...
...that sounds like a suicidal bumblebee?"
(Howard:)Quick, pull the fire alarm,
let's get out of here.
(Sheldon:)Uh, hello again. Um...
(Sheldon:)Yeah, I don't know if women in general...
(Sheldon:)...have been actively discouraged
from pursuing the sciences...
(Sheldon:)...but it's clear you young women
here today have been.
(Sheldon:)While I was listening to my colleagues
waste your time...
(Sheldon:)...it occurred to me that it might be
much more meaningful...
(Sheldon:)...to hear about women in science
from actual women in science.
(Sheldon:)And, uh, I happen to know
two brilliant examples...